Mohamed Safouen Naguez

Web Developer

Skilled React Developer with a focus on frontend development. Accomplished in crafting interactive, visually engaging web applications using React.js and modern web technologies. Dedicated to efficient coding, optimal user experience, and staying up-to-date with industry innovations.



Work Experience



Web Developer

2022 - 2023

I designing and developing user-centric interfaces for our E-SIM provider selling platform using React.js, Figma, and Chakra UI to create efficient, engaging, and consistent designs.



Web Developer

2021 - 2022

Rent-Car Project JavaScript and jQuery with back4app as back-end

Ensure code quality and best practice Manage DataBase with back4app

REST API using JS



Senior technician

2011 - 2021

Maintenance of electronic equipment. Installation of computer and telecommunication

Mount the new computers, to realize the technical assemblies.

Languages

Arabic: Professional working

English: Professional working

French: Professional working

Education

- Web Developement 2021 - Present
- **Senior Technician** 2008 - 2010
- 2nd Year LMD Math-Info 2005 - 2008
- **Mathematics Bachelor** 2004 - 2005

Skills

- React-is
- JavaScript
- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- Chakra Ui
- Tailwind Ui

Contact Info



+216-55-33-93-38



mohamedsafouen@gmail.com



https://mohamedsafouen.github.io/Portofolio/